Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Member Dues Ledgers Collection collection 1903-1982 IBT0049
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Member Dues Ledgers and Local Minute Books collection
1891-1982
1930-1960
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0049
69 Linear Feet
This collection contains bound ledger books from Teamsters Local Unions 14, 366, 572, 606, 686, 700, and 864; earlier Teamsters ledgers collectively list multiple rather than individual Local Unions. Included are cash books, day books, dues books, minutes books, expense books, membership directories, and welfare books. The ledgers date from 1903-1973, with the bulk dating from 1930-1960.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged numerically by Local Union, then alphabetically according to specific type of ledger. Bulk of materials are organized by a specific Local Union, except for earliest dated ledgers consisting of collective rather than individual union records.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains bound ledger books from a variety of Teamsters Local Unions Included are cash books, day books, dues books, minutes books, expense books, membership directories, and welfare books. The ledgers date from 1891-1973, with the bulk dating from 1930-1960.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from IBT 2009 and 2006.
Labor unions; Labor; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Financial statements
- Local 14, ibt0049 series 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of dues, cash and day books of IBT Local 14.
  - Local 14: Cash Books, 1945-1953 (Box 1)
  - Local 14: Day Books, 1946-1952 (Box 2)
  - Local 14: Dues Books, 1941-1944 (Box 3)
  - Local 14: Dues Books, 1945-1948 (Box 4)
- Local 50, 1898-1912; ibt0049 series 2
  This series consists of dues and initiation books for IBT Local 50.
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1898 (Box 64A, Folder 1)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1898-1900 (Box 64A, Folder 2)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1898-1901 (Box 64A, Folder 3)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1904-1905 (Box 64A, Folder 4)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1906-1907 (Box 64A, Folder 5)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1908-1909 (Box 64A, Folder 6)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1910-1912 (Box 64A, Folder 7)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1913-1914 (Box 65A, Folder 1)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1915 - 1916 (Box 65A, Folder 2)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1917 -1918 (Box 66A, Folder 1)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1917 - 1922 (Box 66A, Folder 2)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1923 -1926 (Box 67A, Folder 1)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1927-1930 (Box 67A, Folder 2)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1931-1934 (Box 68A, Folder 1)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1935 - 1937 (Box 68A, Folder 2)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1938 (Box 68A, Folder 3)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1938 - 1939 (Box 68A, Folder 4)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1939 (Box 68A, Folder 5)
  - Local 50: Dues and initiation books, 1939 (Box 68A, Folder 6)
- Local 366, ibt0049 series 3
  This series consists of dues ledgers and minute books of IBT Local 366.
  - Local 366: Cash Books, 1941-1957 (Box 5)
  - Local 366: Day Books, 1947-1950 (Box 6)
  - Local 366: Day Books, 1951-1954 (Box 7)
  - Local 366: Day Books, 1954-1957 (Box 8)
  - Local 366: Day Books, 1957-1961 (Box 9)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1933-1938 (Box 10)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1939-1942 (Box 11)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1943-1946 (Box 12)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1947-1948 (Box 13)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1949-1952 (Box 14)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1949-1952 (Box 15)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1953-1956 (Box 16)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1953-1956 (Box 17)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1957-1960 (Box 18)
  - Local 366: Dues Books, 1957-1960 (Box 19)
  - Local 366: Minute books, 1933-1936 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Local 366: Minute Books, 1936-1938 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Local 366: Minute Books, 1938-1941 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Local 366: Minute Books, 1941-1945 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Local 366: Minute Books, 1945-1948 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Local 336:, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Local 392, ibt0049 series 4
  This series consists of a membership dues ledger for IBT Local 392.
  - Local 392: Membership Ledger, February-April 1913 (Box 71)
- Local 572, ibt0049 series 5
  This series consists of cash books for IBT Local 572.
  - Local 572: Cash Books, January 1950 to December 1953 (Box 70)
  - Local 572: Cash Books, January 1956 to December 1960 (Box 69)
- Local 606, ibt0049 series 6
  This series consists of cash, day, dues and initiation books for IBT Local 606.
  - Local 606: Cash Books, 1913-1939 (Box 20)
  - Local 606: Cash Books, 1939-1950 (Box 21)
  - Local 606: Day Books, 1938-1941 (Box 22)
  - Local 606: Day Books, 1942-1945 (Box 23)
  - Local 606: Day Books, 1945-1948 (Box 24)
  - Local 606: Day Books, 1948-1951 (Box 25)
  - Local 606: Day Books, 1951-1953 (Box 26)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1929-1930 (Box 27)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1929-1932 (Box 28)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1931-1932 (Box 29)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1933-1934 (Box 30)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1933-1936 (Box 31)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1935-1938 (Box 32)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1937-1940 (Box 33)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1941-1944 (Box 34)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1945-1946 (Box 35)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1947-1948 (Box 36)
  - Local 606: Dues Books, 1949-1950 (Box 37)
  - Local 606: Member Directory, undated (Box 38)
  - Local 606: Member Dues and Ledgers Book, 1937 - 1949 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Local 606: Dues and initiation books, 1949-1950 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Local 682, ibt0049 series 7
  This series consists of cash, day, dues and minute books for IBT Local 682.
  - Local 682: Cash Books, 1952-1954 (Box 40)
  - Local 682: Day Books, 1947-1948 (Box 41)
  - Local 682: Day Books, 1949-1950 (Box 42)
  - Local 682: Day Books, 1950-1952 (Box 43)
  - Local 682: Day Books, 1952-1954 (Box 44)
  - Local 682: Day Books, 1953-1954 (Box 45)
  - Local 682: Dues Books, 1947-1948 (Box 46)
  - Local 682: Member Directory, undated (Box 47)
  - Local 682: Minute Books, February 1926-September 1929 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Local 682: Minute Books, November 1963-November 1972 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Local 682: Minute Books, January 1973-May 1976 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Local 682: Minute Books, September 1982 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Local 682: Cash Books, 1947-1952 (Box 39)
- Local 700, ibt0049 series 8
  This series consists of dues, expense, minute and welfare books for IBT Local 700.
  - Local 700: Cash Books, 1936-1952 (Box 48)
  - Local 700: Cash Books, 1952-1961 (Box 49)
  - Local 700: Day Books, 1954-1959 (Box 50)
  - Local 700: Day Books, 1959-1964 (Box 51)
  - Local 700: Day Books, 1964-1969 (Box 52)
  - Local 700: Day Books, 1969-1972 (Box 53)
  - Local 700: Day Books, 1972-1973 (Box 54)
  - Local 700: Dues Books, 1919-1923 (Box 55)
  - Local 700: Dues Books, 1928-1930 (Box 56)
  - Local 700: Dues Books, 1931-1936 (Box 57)
  - Local 700: Dues Books, 1937-1942 (Box 58)
  - Local 700: Dues Books, 1943-1946 (Box 59)
  - Local 700: Dues Books, 1947-1948 (Box 60)
  - Local 700: Expense Books, undated (Box 61)
  - Local 700 Membership Ledger, November 1969-January 1975 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Local 700 Membership Ledger, 1975-1977 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Local 700: Minute Books, September1929-February 1933 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Local 700: Minute Books, September 1936-July 1941 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Local 700: Minute Books, February 1933-September 1936 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Local 700: Minute Books, July 1937-February 1944 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Local 700: Minute Books, August 1941-1947 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Local 700: Minute Books, 1947-1955 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Local 700: Minute Books, January 1961-August 1964 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Local 700: Minute Books, September1964-December 1968 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Local 700: Minute Books, 1968-1970 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Local 700: Welfare Books, 1954-1955 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Local 700: Welfare Books, 1956-1957 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Local 700: Welfare Books, 1958-1962 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Local 700: Welfare Books, 1961-1963 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Local 700: Welfare Books, 1966-1975 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Local 700: Minute Book, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Local 700:, 1950 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Local 864, ibt0049 series 9
  This seriess consists of day books for IBT Local 864.
  - Local 864: Day Books, 1957-1960 (Box 63)
- Local 576, 1925-1944, 1946; ibt0049 series 10
  This series consists of dues and initiation books for IBT Local 576.
  - Local 576: Dues and initiation books, 1925 -1931; Series 10 (Box 71A, Folder 1)
  - Local 576: Dues and initiation books, 1931-1934 (Box 71A, Folder 2)
  - Local 576: Dues and initiation books, 1935 - 1938 (Box 71A, Folder 3)
  - Local 576: Dues and initiation books, 1939 - 1941 (Box 71A, Folder 4)
  - Local 576: Dues and initiation books, 1942 - 1944 (Box 71A, Folder 5)
  - Local 576: Dues and initiation books, 1946 (Box 71A, Folder 6)
- Local 3, 1940 -1941; ibt0049 series 11
  This series consists of dues and initiation books for IBT Local 3.
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1940 (Box 69A, Folder 1)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1941 (Box 69A, Folder 2)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1941 (Box 69A, Folder 3)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1935-1942 (Box 70A, Folder 1)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1942 (Box 70A, Folder 2)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1945 (Box 73A, Folder 1)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1946 (Box 73A, Folder 2)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1944 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1944 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Local 3: Dues and initiation books, 1945 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Local 729, ibt0049 series 12
  This series consists of dues and initiation books for IBT Local 729.
  - Local 729: Dues and initiation books, 1938-1939 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Local 729: Dues and initiation books, 1940 -1941 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Local 729: Dues and initiation books, 1941 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Local 269, ibt0049 series 13
  This series consists of dues and initiation books for IBT Local 269.
  - Local 269: Dues and initation books, 1947 - 1948 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Unidentified Local, ibt0049 series 14
  This series consists of dues and initiation books for an unidentified IBT local union.
  - Unidentified Local: Dues and initiation books, 1945 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Local: Dues and initiation books, 1947 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Multiple Locals Ledger, 1948; Series 14 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified Local: Address Book, 1947-1950; Series 14 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Local 410, ibt0049 series 15
  This series consists of dues and initiation books for IBT Local 410.
  - Local 410: Dues and initiation books, 1946 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Local 832, ibt0049 series 16
  This series consists of dues and initiation books for IBT Local 832.
  - Local 832: Dues and initiation books, 1937 -1938 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Local 832: Dues and initiation books, 1940 - 1942 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Local 191, ibt0049 series 17
  This sweries consists of dues and initiation books for IBT Local 191.
  - Local 191: Dues and initiation books, 1927 - 1930 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Local 191: Dues and initiation books, 1931 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Local 198, ibt0049 series 18
  This series consists of dues and initiation books for IBT Local 198.
  - Local 198: Dues and initiation books, 1947 -1948 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Brewery Local 69, ibt0049 series 19
  This series consists of minyute books for Brewery Workers Local 69.
  - Local 69: Minutes Book, 1891-1897 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Local 69: Minutes Book, 1900 - 1905 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Local 69: Minutes Book, 1905 - 1912 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Local 69: Minutes Book, 1905 - 1912 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Local 17, ibt0049 series 20
  This series consists of a minute book for IBT Local 17.
  - Local 17: Minutes Book, 1900-1901 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Local 597, ibt0049 series 21
  This series consists of a member dues ledger for IBT Local 597.
  - Local 597: Member Dues and Ledger Book, 1941 - 1959 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Brewery Local 23, ibt0049 series 22
  This series consists of a financial ledger for Brewery Workers Local 23.
  - Local 23: Financial Ledger, 1919 - 1925 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Local 392, ibt0049 series 23
  This series consists of a minute book for IBT Local 392.
  - Local 392: Minute Book, 1911 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Local 158, ibt0049 series 24
  This series consists of a cash book for IBT Local 158.
  - Local 158: Cash Book, 1957 -1959 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Local 345, ibt0049 series 25
  This series consists of a minute book for IBT Local 345.
  - Local 345: Minutes Book, 1943-1953 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Joint Council 58
  This series consists of minute books and ledgers from IBT Joint Council 58.
  - JC 58 Minutes Book, 1957 (Box 88, Item 1)
  - JC 58 Cash Book, 1958 (Box 88, Item 2)
  - JC 58 Cash Book, 1950 (Box 88, Item 3)
- Local 367
  This series consists of minute books and ledgers from IBT Local 367.
  - Local 367 Ledger, ND (Box 89, Item 1)
  - Local 367 Ledger, 1937 (Box 89, Item 2)
  - Local 367 Ledger, 1938 (Box 89, Item 3)
- Local 133
  This series consists of ledgers and minutes books from IBT Local 133.
  - Local 133 Ledger, 1933 (Box 90, Item 1)
  - Local 133 Ledger, 1937 (Box 90, Item 2)
  - Local 133 Ledger, 1940 (Box 90, Item 3)
  - Local 133 Ledger, 1937 (Box 90, Item 4)
  - Local 133 Ledger, ND (Box 90, Item 5)
- Local 326
  This series consists of ledgers from IBT Local 326.
  - Local 326 Ledger, ND (Box 91, Item 1)
  - Local 326 Ledger, ND (Box 91, Item 2)
- Local 367
  This series consists of ledgers and minutes books from IBT local 367.
  - Local 367 Ledger, ND (Box 92, Item 1)
  - Local 367 Ledger, 1940-1941 (Box 92, Item 2)
  - Local 367 Ledger, 1939 (Box 92, Item 3)
  - Local 367 Ledger, 1942 (Box 92, Item 4)
  - Local 367 Ledger, 1937 (Box 92, Item 5)
  - Local 367 Ledger, 1939 (Box 92, Item 6)
  - Local 367 Ledger, 1940 (Box 92, Item 7)
  - Local 367 Ledger, ND (Box 92, Item 8)
- Local 393
  This series consists of ledgers and minutes books from IBT Local 393.
  - Local 393 Ledger, 1940 (Box 93, Item 1)
  - Local 393 Minutes Book, 1945-1946 (Box 93, Item 2)
  - Local 393 Ledger, 1937-1938 (Box 93, Item 3)
  - Local 393 Ledger, ND (Box 93, Item 4)
  - Local 393 Ledger, ND (Box 93, Item 5)
  - Local 393 Ledger, 1943 (Box 93, Item 6)
  - Local 393 Minutes Book, 1954 (Box 93, Item 7)
- Local 349
  This series consists of ledgers and minutes books from IBT Local 349.
  - Local 349 Ledger, 1944-1945 (Box 94, Item 1)
  - Local 349 Ledger, 1946-1947 (Box 94, Item 2)
  - Local 349 Ledger, 1940 (Box 94, Item 3)
  - Local 349 Ledger, 1942-1943 (Box 95, Item 1)
  - Local 349 Ledger, 1947 (Box 95, Item 2)
  - Local 349 Ledger, 1937 (Box 95, Item 3)
  - Local 349 Ledger, 1937 (Box 95, Item 4)
- Local 577, IBT 0049
  - Local 577 Ledger Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1966-1973; IBT 0049 Series 33 (Box Shared Box 30, Folder 2)
- Local 41, IBT0049 Series 34
  - Local 41 Dues Cards (3), 1975; IBT0049 Series 34 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Local 94, IBT0049 Series 35
  - Local 94 Dues Cards (2), 1946; IBT 0049 Series 35 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Other Unions, IBT0049 Series 36
  - AFL Dues Cards, 1924; IBT0049 Series 36 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Carpenters Local 1441 Dues Cards, 1921; IBT0049 Series 36 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Finnish Seamen's Union Dues Card, 1936-1938; IBT0049 Series 36 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Association of Machinists Dues Card, 1937-1951; IBT0049 Series 36 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Railway Car Men Local 932, 1918; IBT0049 Series 36 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - UFCW Local 328 Dues Card, IBT 0049 Series 36 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Local 70, IBT 0049 Series 37
  - Local 70: Strike Card, ND; IBT 0049 Series 37 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Local 74, IBT 0049 Series 38
  - Local 74: Withdrawal Card and Transfer Card, 1976-1977; IBT 0049 Series 38 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Local 98, IBT 0049 Series 39
  - Local 98: Dues Cards, 1930; IBT 0049 Series 39 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Local 116, IBT 0049 Series 40
  - Local 116: Withdrawal Card, 1978; IBT 0049 Series 40 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Local 118, IBT 0049 Series 41
  - Local 118: Withdrawal Card, 1940; IBT 0049 Series 41 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Local 169, IBT 0049 Series 42
  - Local 169: Dues Card, 1903; IBT 0049 Series 42 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Local 430, IBT 0049 Series 43
  - Local 430: Member Card, June 1, 1940; IBT 0049 Series 43 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Local 595, IBT 0049 Series 44
  - Local 595: Dues Card, 1945; IBT 0049 Series 44 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Local 710, IBT 0049 Series 45
  - Local 710: Withdrawal Card, 1941; IBT 0049 Series 45 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Local 976, IBT 0049 Series 46
  - Local 976: Dues Card, 1942; IBT 0049 Series 46 (Box 98, Folder 10)